hi i'm bhargav dasgupta
it was a
great pleasure and a privilege to be
here to address the students
of the 1921 batch what i really enjoyed
was this
warmth of
all the faculty and the
excitement and the enthusiasm of the
students it's a beautiful campus
and one thing that really touched me was
the way
the focus of this institute is not just
on education but also on ethical values
the other thing that i really
appreciated was the balance in the batch
46 women managers
and the specialization in insurance we
really need
good managers to come out from some of
these
wonderful institutes like bimtech and
i really hope to see more such
you know institutes which adopt
insurance as a practice and that
enriches the profession of insurance so
it was a great enjoyment and a great
pleasure to be here
and i would love to come back